http://fuelcelltechnologies.com/privacy

My Account
Register
Login
Wish List (0)
$ US Dollar
Fuel Cell Technologies. Inc.
item(s)$0.00
Your shopping cart is empty!
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.fuelcelltechnologies.com and Fuel Cell Technologies, Inc and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all referenced to Fuel Cell Technologies, Inc include www.fuelcelltechnologies.com and FCT. The FCT website is an ecommerce site. By using the FCT website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
FCT may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase FCT’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by FCT. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the FCT website.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through FCT’s public message boards, this information may be collected and use by others.
FCT encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from FCT so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. FCT is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the FCT website.
Use of your Personal Information
FCT collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
FCT may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from FCT and its affiliates. FCT may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
FCT does not sell, rent, or lease its customer lists to third parties.
FCT may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to FCT, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information
FCT may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit with FCT, in order to determine what FCT services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within FCT to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
FCT will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on FCT or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights of property of FCT; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of FCT, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The FCT website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize FCT pages, or register with FCT site or services, a cookie helps FCT to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same FCT website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the FCT features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the FCT services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Verisign
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets layer (SSL) protocol.
Verisign is an independent, third-party company engaged in the development of digital trust. Verisign provides authentication of Internet services, digital identity and intellectual property. By clicking on the Verisign logo, the Verisign website will serve up a web page that confirms that FCT is “Verisign Authenticated.”
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from FCT by contacting us at fuelcell@aol.com.
Changes to this Statement
FCT will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. FCT encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how FCT is protecting your information.
Contact Information
FCT welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that FCT has not adhered to this Statement, please contact FCT at:
Fuel Cell Technologies, Inc
5620 Venice Ave, NE, Suite F
Albuquerque, New Mexico 87113
Email Address:
fuelcell@aol.com
Telephone number:
(505) 821-4762
Continue
About
You can change this text from Control Panel Social band > About text Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat.""" """"""""""
Information
About Us
Return Information
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Customer Service
Customer Support
Contact Us
Powered By NFG Media Fuel Cell Technologies. Inc.
© 2020
